http://lucene.apache.org/privacy.html

TM
Core (Java)
Solr
PyLucene
Ultra-fast Search Library and Server
Apache Lucene and Solr set the standard for search and indexing performance
Proven search capabilities
Our core algorithms along with the Solr search server power applications the world over, ranging
from mobile devices to sites like Twitter, Apple and Wikipedia.
Large, Vibrant community
The goal of Apache Lucene and Solr is to provide world class search capabilities
Apache 2.0 licensed
Apache Lucene and Solr are distributed under a commercially friendly Apache Software license
Privacy Policy
Information about your use of this website is collected using server access logs and a tracking cookie. The collected information consists of the following:
The IP address from which you access the website;
The type of browser and operating system you use to access our site;
The date and time you access our site;
The pages you visit; and
The addresses of pages from where you followed a link to our site.
Part of this information is gathered using a tracking cookie set by the Google Analytics service and handled by Google as described in their privacy policy. See your browser documentation for instructions on how to disable the cookie if you prefer not to share this data with Google.
We use the gathered information to help us make our site more useful to visitors and to better understand how and when our site is
used. We do not track or collect personally identifiable information or associate gathered data with any personally identifying information from other sources.
By using this website, you consent to the collection of this data in the manner and for the purpose described above.
Lucene Core (Java)
Solr
PyLucene
Open Relevance (Discontinued)
Copyright © 2011-2020 The Apache Software Foundation, Licensed under
the Apache License, Version 2.0.
Privacy Policy
Apache and the Apache feather logo are trademarks of The Apache Software Foundation.
Apache Lucene, Apache Solr and their
respective logos are trademarks of the Apache Software Foundation.
Please see the Apache Trademark Policy
for more information.
